[ Watch on KissFlix.co ]
Interschool champion, take it easy.
Well played.
Your brother plays all right.
I happen to beat a champion.
He plays tennis well.
It's too bad he's from a less privileged background.
No wonder he lacks manners.
-What did you say? -Am I wrong?
-Say it again. -Hey.
-Why is your brother so rude? -It's okay.
Someone isn't good at tennis but is great at picking fights.
The Speaker's son.
He started it.
A bit of advice.
Think before you speak.
Don't shame your family.
Won't you offend him?
So what? I've been sick of him for ages.
I'll rise higher than him anyway.
What's the fear?
He wasn't wrong.
Others have never seen me as a part of the Hsueh family.
Don't say that.
Dad will know how amazing you are one day.
We'll do big things together as brothers.
Do big things?
You're putting it away? I haven't smoked you.
Oh, so you want to be smoked too?
I have a better idea.
THE FIXERS
BACKSTABBER
HOWIE, MISSED CALL
ONE NEW VOICEMAIL
Dad, hurry back.
There's trouble.
Police station. Hello.
I want to file a report.
My child is innocent.
-He doesn't know anything. -I will leave
when I get the answer I want.
Hey, it's the police.
Is something going on inside? Someone reported a disturbance here.
Speak carefully,
and I'll let your son go.
If anyone is home, please open the door.
Coming!
Neighbors said there was noise coming from here.
Noise?
Maybe I got too loud while hosting live shopping streams.
May I enter and take a look?
Nothing happened, right?
There's no need.
I'll leave you alone.
Tell me when the goods arrive.
Okay.
-Everything's okay? -Yeah.
Mind your volume.
Okay, thank you.
Howie!
Howie! Are you okay?
Howie, you're scaring me! Howie!
Get up!
Answer me! You're scaring me!
Howie!
-Fuck. -Honey, what do we do?
Who exactly were they?
No, I'm telling the police.
You can't.
Why not?
What exactly did you do?
The bribery case against Chao Ming-cheng continues to escalate.
Thackery Huang, chairman of Ching He, was allegedly a middleman.
Further digging by prosecutors revealed
that he might be involved in more than one case.
The latest evidence shows that…
I'm giving you a chance to explain.
Who exactly were they?
When our son wakes up,
we will leave here.
What if he doesn't wake up?
What if our son doesn't wake up?
Just how much are you hiding from me?
You're not Mr. Goldie's bodyguard, are you?
We are partners.
What kind of partners?
We work for Ching He.
Ching He?
You're here.
It's been a while since we had a drink.
Wait, it's just the two of us today.
We shouldn't have this.
So you have decided to help me get the Primordial Files?
As Dad said, I am a Hsueh too. Who would help you if I didn't?
Besides, I joined Ching He
so that I could help the family one day.
I've always known you're the only one I can trust.
If Dad knew about this, he'd be so happy.
What you're doing isn't just for Dad, is it?
It's for yourself too, right?
When you first entered politics, I thought Dad forced you.
I didn't expect you to be so ambitious.
Look at this bridge.
It connects two sides of the city.
One side represents power and order.
The other, opportunity and ambition.
Dad believes it's not opposition,
but symbiosis.
But to me,
coexistence is just a form of compromise.
The strong are meant to set the rules for the world.
What I want to do
is to take down the bridge,
so that there is no separation.
Everyone plays by the same rules.
And I get to set them.
I'm just like you.
I don't want to just rely on Dad.
I have my own vision.
If you want me to help you, promise me one thing.
Go ahead.
Don't touch Felix Chiang and Mina Shen.
Seems like Yeh Yueh Tong hasn't told you everything.
It's okay. I promise you.
Are you okay?
Luckily, my son survived.
But he's still unconscious.
The doctor said the next 48 hours will be critical.
I saw the news. Thackery was arrested.
A new Celestial is coming.
Madam Fan is replacing Thackery as head of Ching He.
What happened?
Madam Fan's father used to lead Ching He.
Now she wants to reclaim the position of Fixer Celestial.
So is it too late to give this to Thackery?
What is that?
Zoe gave this to me
before she died.
Did you read the files?
Not yet.
Zoe wanted me
to hand it over to Thackery.
Give it to me. I'll give it to Thackery.
He was arrested.
How will you give it to him?
I've arranged to visit the detention center.
Zoe said the contents…
are related to your family.
And I've just confirmed
that the Hsueh family was behind Thackery's arrest.
What's on this card might stop Madam Fan from becoming Fixer Celestial.
Trust me.
When Howie wakes up,
I will take him and his mother…
away from here.
CHING HE TEMPLE
We were able to get Thackery detained
thanks to you, Sir Hong.
Without you, it wouldn't have gone so smoothly.
It's time for Ching He to move past the old and usher in the new.
You have been through thick and thin with Ching He.
I guarantee that I will bring a lot to Ching He.
With the Hsueh family as Ching He's ally,
things will be much easier.
It's just that Thackery won't step down.
If Madam Fan wants to take over,
there are still some uncertainty.
With the Hsueh family's backing, we are stronger.
But Ching He has always remained neutral.
That's something to keep in mind.
I wasn't sure about saying this,
but now that we have you, Sir Hong,
everything will be fine.
I heard that the head of Ching He has two keys.
Thackery has one of them.
Where is the other one?
It's with me.
Are you willing to hand it over now?
It's not yet time for the inauguration ceremony.
Handing it over now doesn't feel right, does it?
Sir Hong,
we have already come this far.
We can't afford any slipups.
I understand.
Do you think he will hand it over?
If he has agreed to help me,
he will make the right choice.
Sir Hong's family has been with Ching He for generations.
No one could become Ching He's leader without his assistance.
Now I can rest easy.
Oh, right.
I heard two people have been giving you a headache.
A headache? Who?
Felix Chiang and Mina Shen.
Louis wanted me
to ask you to spare them.
But he didn't tell me why you're after them.
So I'm curious.
They know something about an important client of mine.
I merely gave them a warning.
Since Louis has asked,
of course I will help.
But I'm also curious what his role is in all of this.
If Thackery doesn't step down,
Louis could help.
That's what he wants in return.
I got it.
Thank you, Chairwoman.
You're welcome,
Mayor.
It's a pleasure working with you.
Did you know?
Zoe is dead.
What she wanted to give you is in my possession.
But I didn't quite expect what's inside.
So what do you plan to do now?
Since it has to do with the Hsueh family…
you can't have it.
Are you going to betray Ching He?
When I joined Ching He, I told you
the Hsueh family would need me one day.
I never thought it would be like this.
Do you know
why I let you join Ching He
even though I knew you were a Hsueh?
You wanted to use me to deal with the Hsuehs.
You're different from your brother.
Over the years,
your performance in Ching He
hasn't disappointed me.
Even now,
in my eyes,
you are still the same Louis.
Are you so sure?
My brother made me a tempting offer.
I will always be a Hsueh. You know that.
If you step down,
I can guarantee your safety.
You don't have to bother.
I know that my time has passed.
I just hope that Ching He can remain stable.
If that requires me to step down, then I will.
I only worry that if the Primordial Files fall into the wrong hands,
the balance of the world will be broken.
If that happens, I fear no one will be able to save it.
Leave that to the next head of Ching He.
Do you really think
the Hsuehs will spare those who know about their secret
if they find out about the video?
The mayor has started asking.
Make sure there are no loose ends.
After Thackery steps down,
those who know about the Hsuehs' secret
must not remain, understand?
Got it.
Feeling better?
Goldie?
The doctor said they're just minor wounds.
Luckily, no brain injury.
He should be able to go home soon.
I'm close to the head of neurology here.
I'll ask him to come and take a look.
Why haven't you been over for dinner lately?
Howie, don't be rude.
When you feel better, I'll come over.
But it doesn't seem to be safe at home now.
Don't worry. They won't come again.
Did you come to see my husband for something?
Didn't he say he's quitting?
I came to say goodbye to him.
I will handle the rest myself.
Why are you here?
Did you see Thackery?
Thackery has agreed to step down.
Madam Fan will take over.
Was it voluntary?
He had no choice.
What about the video?
Did you give it to him?
You know about the video. They won't spare you.
There is still time before Madam Fan takes over.
They won't act yet.
-Take your family and go. -So you didn't give him the video.
So now you want to help…
help the Hsuehs and Madam Fan take over Ching He.
This isn't something you should worry about.
I've bought you time.
Do you know how many people got hurt because of this?
Fuck, I trusted you and thought you were a brother!
Fuck!
This is for my son.
For Zoe and her daughter!
And Ben!
All this just for the chairman position of Ching He!
Is it worth so many lives?
Fucking bastard!
Take your family and go.
Fuck.
Where is your mom?
She went to buy food. She'll be back soon.
You're still studying? Doesn't your head hurt?
I'll still have exams when I'm discharged.
It's all because I'm useless.
I failed to protect you and your mom.
Hey, listen.
Next time this happens,
the first thing you should do is run.
Run quickly, understand?
Dad,
I know that if it were you,
you would return to save Mom too.
But I know you had more important things to handle.
-He left? -Yeah.
Hey.
Get Howie's discharge papers tomorrow.
Let's get out of here for a bit.
You fought with your partner?
Get away from here for a while?
So how long are we going to hide?
It's one thing for the two of us,
but do you want our son to hide with us forever?
Take care of your business.
Or do you plan to wait until your hand tremors worsen?
I've been with you for so many years.
You think I don't know you?
I also know
you've been looking after Chi's family.
I'm just upset
that you're keeping this from me.
I'll handle the discharge in a few days and take our son to my mother's.
Sort out your situation before then
and return safely.
Do you hear me?
Don't worry.
Until you get back,
I will protect your wife.
Don't copy your dad's nonsense.
It'll be fine. Hang on.
Hang in there, you hear me?
At worst,
we do it ourselves.
Lord Guan,
get me out alive.
Do it properly.
Remember.
Swamp Eel, long time no see.
Aren't you a bit old to be running the streets?
I'm here for your boss.
I'm here to ask a favor.
For whom?
Your old acquaintance,
Thackery Huang.
How do you want me to help you?
Stop Fan from taking over Ching He.
Are you out of your mind? You want to drag San He in?
If San He intervenes,
that's declaring war on the Hsueh family and Yeh Yueh Tong.
Don't forget.
You guys deposed the elder Fan back then
and supported Thackery.
If you now let Fan take over,
you might be in trouble.
Besides, you should know very well
what kind of person Fan is.
If we can't play fair, we fight dirty.
Now that's different.
ARCADE
Did Louis send you here?
No.
I want to see you.
We have a common enemy.
I can help you take out Madam Fan.
Why?
That motherfucker went after my family.
At least you still have people you can protect.
It's fine.
I shouldn't have come.
Ben wouldn't want you to avenge him.
I'll go with you.
Those two know I won't let that go easily.
At worst, when we finally meet,
they will nag at me.
I told you, we're here to visit.
Must I repeat myself?
You're not family. You can't enter.
Since when is that a rule?
Quiet. Don't disturb other patients.
Don't be like this. You make it seem like we're here to collect debts.
You look like debt collectors.
Who brings fruit to collect debts?
-Ma'am. -Milky.
Sorry, nurse, we know each other.
Smile. You looked scary, so she got the wrong idea.
Tell them to quiet down.
Okay. Sorry. Thank you.
Why did you bring so many people?
Well, Loach called and said he had stuff to deal with.
He sent me here to protect you.
The fruit!
Damn it, bring it inside. Don't make her hold it.
Why do you only eat blood pudding and deep-fried tofu for tien-bu-la?
After my parents passed away, I was forced to live with my aunt.
Her favorite thing to cook was radish and pork meatball soup.
I've heard Ben mention it.
That big mouth.
I told him that after I retire,
I'd open a swamp eel noodle stall next to his.
He hated the idea.
Before he died, he mentioned the stall to me.
He probably meant to say it to you.
You didn't invite me here
just for small talk, right?
I heard
that you want to replace Thackery
and become Ching He's new chairwoman.
The news spread fast.
It seems that San He has eyes and ears everywhere.
This is a big deal for San He.
No matter who takes over,
we will continue to count on Ching He's support whenever needed.
No problem.
We each take a spot.
Shoot whenever there's a chance.
If one of us fails, there will still be a second chance.
San He and Ching He have always had strong ties.
But don't forget.
If my father hadn't insisted on allying with you despite the objections,
we wouldn't have become so close.
Of course I remember.
My brother speaks highly of your father.
We're forever grateful.
So why bite the hand that feeds you?
I still remember how you worked with Thackery
to accuse me of killing our own fixers.
Do you intend to do it again?
Put down the gun, or I'll shoot.
Madam Fan can't die.
So this is how San He shows hospitality.
A misunderstanding.
There must be a huge misunderstanding.
Hey, go down and take a look.
Next time, come to my place.
At least it will be safer.
I won't bother them while they catch up.
Damn it. It'll be harder next time.
Fuck!
Sir Hong,
are you a traitor too?
Everything has been taken care of.
Looks like all that's left is the inauguration ceremony.
Thank you for your support, Chairwoman.
And I must thank your brother for saving me.
Everything's set. Now we just wait for Sir Hong to organize the inauguration.
The Thackery I know won't comply so easily.
I'm worried that when he is released from custody,
he will play other tricks.
Too bad we don't know where he hid his key.
Thackery's ring is his key.
It's just that the ring hasn't been found.
If Thackery hid his key,
only Sir Hong would know where it might be.
Sometimes, the most dangerous place is the safest.
It should be in Ching He Temple.
Your brother said
you helped him a lot.
Good.
You have finally come around.
Isn't this what you wanted most?
Tristan can finally carry on your family legacy.
Do you know
how many people want to use our family to climb the ladder?
Or even replace us?
Dad,
if Tristan went down the wrong path trying to reach the top,
would you still support him?
I forced your brother onto this path.
If he went astray,
I would be to blame too.
Is this what you want or what he wants?
We are all doing this for the Hsueh family.
To protect this family,
sometimes you have to remove a few pebbles along the way
for the greater good.
Louis…
my days are numbered.
Your brother's path forward
now depends on the two of you.
Dad, don't worry.
Leave it to us brothers. Get some rest.
INVITATION, CHING HE FIXER CELESTIAL INAUGURATION
CELESTIAL, EARTH, SOLAR, LUNAR
Subtitle translation by: Hannah Liu